Angaar Uriakhil

Address: 35 Moulton Avenue, Hounslow, Middlesex, TW3 4LN, United Kingdom **Mobile**: 07853941603 **Email**: angar1996@gmail.com **LinkedIn**: Link **Github**: Link

Profile:

A recent graduate with a first-class master's degree in Chemical Engineering, with a passion for sustainability and programming experience. A person who constantly pursues self-development and that can be relied upon to complete any task, no matter the complexity.

Education and Qualifications:

University of Surrey, Guildford

September 2016 - June 2020

Chemical Engineering MEng (Hons.) - First Class

Academic Achievements:

- Published master' thesis on PFAS treatment in the scientific journal *Chemosphere*, available <u>here</u>.
- Member of STARS development scheme due to outstanding academic performance.
- Design Report (Role: Layout Engineer on the Claus Process) (Grade: 70%).

Lampton School, Hounslow

September 2008 - May 2016

GCSEs

11 GCSE's, A*-C, incl. English Language (A), Maths (A), Core Science (A), Additional Science (A*)

A-Levels

Mathematics (B), Chemistry (B), Biology (B), and English Literature (B) [English only at AS-Level]

Key Skills:

- Computer literate:
 - ✓ **Python & Javascript** Completed several online courses (FreeCodeCamp, Codecademy, etc) in both languages. I recently developed a <u>chemistry-focused application</u> using Python.
 - ✓ **Python Pandas** I can index databases using the pandas module for powerful data analysis.
 - ✓ Also proficient in technologies: *Git, SQLite3, HTML5, CSS3* (including Flexbox & Bootstrap).
 - ✓ Proficient in *Microsoft Word, Excel, Visio, PowerPoint*. Comfortable with advanced functions such as *IF, GOALSEEK, VLOOKUP* and using *Pivot Tables* and *Solver* in *Excel*.
 - ✓ Experienced in using process simulation software such as **Aspen HYSYS** and **CHEMCAD**.
- **Driving:** Holder of a full UK driving license and a regular driver since September 2016.
- Languages: Fluent in Farsi and English, Advanced in Urdu/Hindi. Basic in German.
- **Electronics repair:** Competent at electronics disassembly, using a multimeter and soldering.

Certifications:

- ✓ Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures (<u>FreeCodeCamp</u>)
- ✓ Scientific Computing with Python (<u>FreeCodeCamp</u>)
- ✓ Responsive Web Design (<u>FreeCodeCamp</u>)
- ✓ LinkedIn Assessment badges in Javascript, Python, Git, OOP, MS Excel, Word, PowerPoint.

Work Experience

Seller/Technician (e-commerce shop)

October 2020 - December 2020

- Repaired electronic devices by using problem-solving skills, & specialist tools (e.g. multimeter).
- Solely responsible for organising item shipping, tracking, pricing, handling customer enquiries.
- Calculated profitability for each item using Excel.

Shift Manager - University of Surrey Pilot Plant (Module work)

May 2019 - May 2019

- Acted safely and professionally by applying appropriate PPE while on a plant environment.
- As manager, worked effectively as a team by instructing two shift hands via radio to ensure continued production of saline solution. Made logical decisions under alarm pressure by simultaneously monitoring controllers and interpreting a plant manual/mass balance.

AS Mathematics/Chemistry Tutor - Freelance

July 2018 - October 2018

- Tailored lessons to the student by identifying difficult topics to focus on from the specification, based on my own previous experience and student feedback.
- Distilled complex topics into simple lessons and supported student by positive reinforcement.
- Consolidated knowledge by solving example questions in each session and setting homework.

Personal Reference: Dr Bahman Amini Horri, University of Surrey (b.aminihoori@surrey.ac.uk).